bigdoggamer.com 2011-02-23

# Privacy Policy | BigDogGamer.com

## Privacy Policy

**I. General**

The BigDog respects the privacy of every individual who visits our website or purchases products online. This statement of our privacy policies outlines the information BigDog Products will collect and how BigDog Products will use that information. This policy statement will also instruct you on what to do if you want BigDog Products to remove your personal information collected or stored during previous visits to the BigDog Gamer website.

**II. Use of Personal Information**

BigDog Products will not collect or retain any information about you personally (that is, your name, address, telephone number, or email address) unless you provide it to us voluntarily. If you do not want any personal information collected, please do not submit it to us. If you have already submitted this information and would like us to remove it from our records, please [contact us](http://bigdoggamer.com/contact/). We will use reasonable efforts to delete your information from our existing files. If you do provide us with personal information, we may retain and use that information for several purposes. First, we may store and process the information insure our warranty and quality controls are aligned to better understand your needs and how we can improve our products and services. Your email address or other contact information will not be provided to any one.

**III. Individuals under 18yrs of age**

BigDog Products does not intend to collect any personal information (such as name, address, telephone number, age, or email address) from persons younger than 18 years of age. If a parent or guardian of a child who has provided us with such information would like the information deleted from our records, he or she should [contact us ](http://bigdoggamer.com/contact/). We will make reasonable efforts to delete the child’s information from our existing files.
